♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Good morning!
Is what
normal families say.
Lois, I'll take
my breakfast to go.
I'm going fishing
with the fellas.
Peter, I thought we
were going to have
some family time
this weekend.
You're going
fishing again?
Yes, Lois. I love fishing.
Remember, fishing was
my not-at-all-memorable job
for two years?
- No.
You don't remember
my fishing boat?
Santos and Pasqual?
Not even a little.
They were like
male Consuelas.
It was a mistake making 'em
Portuguese, though.
People don't even know
what a Portuguese is.
(chairs creaking)
That's what I thought
a Portuguese was.
Me and my brain, huh?
And we're just
getting started!
(birds squeaking,
foghorn blowing)
Boy, it's not like Quagmire
to be this late.
Yeah.
Jeez, I've never tried
to make conversation
with just Joe before.
This is brutal.
Come on, Joe,
you're losing him.
Think of something.
This was your shot.
Two thirds
of the planet is water.
Yeah.
Two thirds
of the planet is water?
This guy's okay.
All right, well, um,
we should probably go find out
what's keeping Quagmire.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
And you know, Joe,
uh, I was thinking.
Maybe one night we get
dinner, just the two of us.
I would like that.
(knocking)
PETER: Hey, Quagmire?
You in there?
(gasps)
Holy crap!
Oh, my God!
He must have autoerotically
asphyxiated himself!
Yeah, while he was
watching clown porn.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh yeah, baby!
You make me so horny!
(bicycle horn blowing)
Come on, help me get him down!
Peter, he's still alive!
We got to get him
to a hospital!
All right, but let's just watch
the end of this clown porn first.
(calliope music playing)
Oh, Peter, we came
as soon as we heard.
How is he?
He's in a coma, Lois.
My God, what the hell happened?
He hung himself during
autoerotic asphyxiation.
Just goes to show anything
can be dangerous.
Is his family here?
His sister Brenda is coming
with her boyfriend, Jeff.
Oh, my God, not that guy.
Is she still with him?
Isn't he the one
that beats her?
Yeah, but she's
gotten a lot better.
All right, on the way back,
I get to pick the radio station,
because that was awful.
I know, yeah, it
was, I'm sorry.
Oh, God, I just...
I hope Glenn's okay.
I'm so worried about him.
Shut up and limp!
We're in a handicapped spot,
you slut!
Well, Miss Quagmire,
your brother Glenn
is lucky to be alive.
You know, we're all lucky to be
alive on such a beautiful day.
In fact, nurse--
all surgeries are outside today.
You know, when we were kids,
our mother used to sing
a song when we were sad.
Maybe that'll help now.
Come on, Brenda,
a stupid nursery rhyme
isn't going to wake him up,
especially the way you sing.
(laughing)
Right, man?
Gyaaaa.
♪ Glenn, don't die from
autoerotic asphyxiation ♪
♪ Your friends want to
go fishing with you... ♪
This song is from childhood?
♪ Live to see tomorrow,
October 31, 2011. ♪
Where am I?
What happened?
Oh, Glenn!
Oh, thank God
you're all right!
Hey, you touching
my girl?!
Relax, Jeff.
That's her brother.
Yeah, that's how it starts.
Come on, Brenda, we
got to get out of here.
I need cigarettes
and jeans.
Oh, thanks, you guys, for all
your help through this.
Oh, Glenn, we're just
so glad you're all right.
And Jeff and I are happy
to stay here with you
for as long as you need.
Fine, then you call
my cousin Terry
and tell him we're not going
to be at his karate recital!
Well, Jeff,
he is my brother.
Why do you always got to remind
me I didn't finish high school?
Well, listen, how about I make
us all some dinner, huh?
Come here!
(clattering)
You fat, ugly bitch!
If today
wasn't your birthday...
Jeff! Please,
you're being...
What?!
What am I being?!
Crazy?!
Unemployed?!
Why don't you call the cops
like you did on Christmas?!
I-I-I didn't call them!
They were called!
Oh, now you're calling me a liar
in front of this cat?!
I got another cat.
Aw, that yellow lab
looks like it's dying.
Peter,
that's Gwyneth Paltrow.
She's fine.
Look, turn off the light.
I just want to get to sleep and
put this ugly night behind us.
All that unpleasantness
with Brenda and Jeff
was more than I can handle.
It's no big deal, Lois.
We probably just caught
'em on an off night.
JEFF: Where do you get
off calling me a deadbeat
in front of your brother?!
BRENDA: No, Jeff, a-a-all I said was
that you were in between jobs!
JEFF:
Well, it wouldn't matter
if you'd just pick up that
night shift at the prison!
BRENDA: But then I'll be working
a hundred hours a week.
JEFF:
So what?!
I need money for motor oil
and wallet chains!
BRENDA:
Okay, I'll ask about it Monday.
Can I put my nightgown
back on?
JEFF:
No, I'm not done drawing!
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Peter.
Geez, Quagmire,
you look terrible.
Oh, I didn't get any sleep.
Hi, Glenn.
How are you?
Not great, Lois.
I'm stuck in the middle of some
bad stuff with my sister.
I know, it sounded like there
was quite a ruckus going on
over there last night.
That Jeff seems like
kind of a monster.
Yeah, that guy's scary
as an Iraq Lobster.
(playing "Rock Lobster")
♪ Death to America ♪
♪ And butter sauce ♪
♪ Don't boil me ♪
♪ I'm still alive ♪
♪ Iraq Lobster ♪
♪ Iraq Lobster. ♪
I've tried talking to Brenda
about leaving him,
but I haven't
gotten anywhere.
I was actually hoping
you could talk to her, Lois.
She might open up more to you,
you know, 'cause you're a woman.
- Me?
- Yeah, would you mind at least trying?
Well, I guess she does
need someone to talk to.
Well, let's hope
she's good at talking
'cause we know she doesn't
listen so good.
That... we know.
You know, Brenda, I'm glad
we could get together.
Me, too, Lois.
It's nice to have a
girlfriend to chat with.
Don't you have any
back home?
Oh, no. Jeff would
never allow that.
You know, that's kind of what
I want to talk to you about,
Brenda.
Do you mind
taking off your sunglasses?
Oh, my God.
No, i-it's really
not that bad.
It only hurts when I see.
You know, you don't have
to stay with a man
who treats you that way.
Oh, Jeff's sweet.
You don't see how soft and gentle
he hits me when we're alone.
Do you hear yourself?
He shouldn't be
hitting you at all.
I don't think you understand
how serious a matter...
Close your menu.
What?
Close your menu, so they
know we're ready to order.
I'll give you
another moment.
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shoot.
See, this is why Jeff
corrects me all the time.
Corrects you?
Brenda, he's not correcting you,
he's beating you!
Well, I-I-I can see
why you'd think that
'cause of the punches and all,
but it's just that Jeff's been
so angry about immigrants.
What?!
It'll be better when
he gets back to work.
Our relationship is just
complicated, that's all.
No, Brenda,
it's not complicated.
Trying to get
a straight answer
out of a 23-year-old
girl is complicated.
So, do you want
to go out some time?
Out like, go out or hang out
or just do something?
Like a date.
Like a date date?
Or like a date?
Both, I... I guess.
Yeah, sure, maybe.
I don't know. Yes, no.
Here's the first three
digits of my phone number.
E-mail me.
Joe, the guy's a menace.
They've been with me
three days now,
and all he does is beat her
day and night.
And on top of that,
they say they don't need
to be entertained,
but then they're always like,
"Hey, so what're we doing?
What's next?"
Hey, Joe, can't you...
can't you just arrest the guy?
I can't arrest Jeff
unless Brenda files a formal
complaint with the police.
She won't go to the police.
She's afraid
of what Jeff will do.
And to be honest,
I don't blame her.
I mean, w-w-what happens
if one of these nights,
he hits her so hard
he kills her?
Sorry, Quagmire.
Police policy, we can't step
in until it's too late.
But if I were you, I'd
set up an intervention.
What's that?
It's like a surprise
birthday party,
but instead of cake and
presents, there's angry letters
and someone who
inappropriately tries
to make it about themselves.
Aw, that sounds great!
I bet I would really shine
at one of those.
All right, well, first
we want to thank you all
for being here for Brenda.
Now, I know it's going
to be a long day,
but we're all here because we
care about her very much.
What the... what's going on?
What's all this?
Brenda, this is
an intervention.
A lot of us don't like how
Jeff's been treating you.
So we're going
to say a few things,
and then you'll say a few
things, and then we'll be done.
Sound good?
Um...
I guess.
All right, so we're going to go
around the room and tell you
exactly how your situation
has affected each of us.
Meg?
I feel like if he likes you,
maybe you can change him.
Okay, maybe she wasn't
the one to start with.
Caleb?
Caleb, you want
to go ahead?
M... M... me?
Yeah, go ahead.
Uh... It's Chris.
Y-You don't know my name?
All right, this isn't off
to a flying start.
Peter, why don't you go ahead?
So, you like
getting beaten, huh?
Well, why don't you smoke a
whole carton of cigarettes!
Look, I know what you guys
are trying to do,
but Jeff and I are fine.
No, Brenda,
you're not fine, okay?
Please, I'd like to say
something, if I may.
(clearing throat)
"Brenda, the fact that
you are being abused
"has affected my life
in the following ways:
"The sister that I knew
and loved growing up
"no longer exists.
"The person I see before me now
is just a punching bag.
"And I call you 'person'
and not 'woman'
"because a woman is a strong,
beautiful, vibrant creature.
"A woman embraces life.
"A woman makes choices
to make her life better.
"Sadly, the fact that you are
with Jeff, proves to me
that you have made a choice
to make your life worse."
I-I want the girl
I grew up with back.
I want... I want my sister back.
Brenda, I love you.
Please make the right decision.
Which is a perfect time
for me to tell my jokes.
Peter!
And I will save
them for the end.
Glenn, I am so lucky
to have such a wonderful,
loving brother like you.
So, are you gonna
leave him?
Oh, there you are!
Hey, give me some money!
I saw a cool bandana.
What the hell's going on here?!
Listen here, you bully!
For your information,
Brenda just agreed
to leave you!
Like hell she did.
Brenda, you tell 'em?
No, not yet.
Everyone...
I have wonderful news.
Jeff and I are getting married.
(all gasp)
I'd show you the ring,
but it's under the splint.
My finger fell down the stairs.
You're getting married?!
Yeah, but only 'cause
she's pregnant.
Pregnant?!
Oh, congratulations!
Have you thought
of any names yet?
Maybe... maybe
"Slappy"?
Or-or "Bruisey"?
Or "Keep-It-Down-
In-There-sy"?
Guys, what the hell
am I gonna do?
She can't marry
that bastard.
He's just gonna
keep beatin' her,
and then he's gonna beat
the kid, too!
God, I wish she'd never met
Jeffrey Fecalman.
You know, I was
thinking... Wait, what?
What?
That's his name?
Yeah.
Huh-larious.
But you know,
I was thinking this afternoon,
what the hell happened to the
days when a guy does something
like that to a girl, and a bunch
of us guys get together
and just go kick
his (bleep) ass?
Boy, that'd be
satisfying.
Well... why not?
What do you mean?
The three of us.
We go over there
and we do what's right;
we kill the bastard.
Whoa, whoa, Quagmire.
You know, I could arrest
you just for saying that.
You know what else
you can get arrested for?
Soliciting a rooster.
I don't know what this
cock-a-doodle-doo thing is,
but it sounds gay
and it sounds scatological.
I'm in.
You're about to
have a neat day.
Quagmire, you're talking
about murdering a guy.
It doesn't matter
what he's done,
it's still murder.
No, Joe, it does matter
what he's done!
These kinds of guys
don't change.
Y-you think they ever suddenly
wake up and realize
the error of their ways
and clean up their act? No!
They just keep ruining
everyone's lives,
and the world is better off
without 'em.
It's against the
law, Quagmire,
and that's the
end of it.
(loud slap, Brenda screams)
JEFF: What the hell?!
Did you change the channel
while I was going
to get a beer?!
Oh, yeah, I-I'm sorry,
honey, I just wanted
to see who was
on Letterman.
We're watching Leno,
you bitch!
I'm so sorry!
His soft, gentle humor
connects effortlessly
with my mainstream
sensibilities!
(slaps)
(screams)
Let's waste this dick.
Boy, everything's different now
than it used to be, isn't it?
You know, this morning I had
a bowl of Fruity Pebbles cereal.
Yeah, yeah. When I was a kid,
they were boulders!
(laughs loudly)
(laughs)
Cereals do change.
Oh, no, no. Here's something,
here's something.
Did you hear about this?
Here's a bunch
of words in a row:
because the economy's so bad,
they've decided they're gonna
shut down all the prisons.
Yeah, yeah.
And-and they're gonna send
all the inmates to Congress.
I don't get that one!
Hi, there, Jeff.
Hey, what's going
on, dudes?
Brenda just fell.
Get your lazy ass up and get
my neighbors some beers!
Actually, we don't
have time, Jeff.
We were just about
to go on
our annual midnight
hunting trip.
We thought you might
want to join us.
Yeah, what the hell.
Go shoot some animals,
that sounds like fun.
Hey, it beats sitting at home
watching Meg pop her zits.
(squish)
Okay, okay,
who would you rather do?
Dame Judi Dench with 30 minutes
of kissing first
or Eddie Izzard in drag,
but he has a working vagina?
Would Eddie Izzard tell
others about it?
Eddie Izzard is very discreet.
Then that's your answer.
You know, Quagmire,
I gotta say,
I was pretty surprised
you wanted me to come along.
I thought
you hated my guts.
(chuckles)
Oh, come on, Jeff,
I don't hate your
(bleep) guts.
Well, then what the hell
are we doing out here?
I thought we were gonna kill...
Ah!
So, Jeff, do you
like loud sentences?!
I guess.
I gotta take a whiz.
All right, look,
when he comes back,
I'm just gonna
do it, okay?
I'm just gonna point my gun
straight at his head
before he even knows
what's going on.
(shotgun racks)
Kinda like this?
You know, Quagmire,
you are pathetic.
You have to bring
your friends out here with you
to do your dirty work?
What... what do you mean, Jeff?
You're gonna kill me,
is that it?
Uh-uh!
Not unless you want
your friend's brains
all over the place!
Listen, Jeff,
just put the gun down
and we'll forget this whole
thing, okay?
Oh. Well, that's never
happened before.
Kinda don't know
what to do next.
So now you'll forget
the whole thing?
Yeah, I, uh, guess
that is what I said.
No, no, we can't forget
the whole thing!
Yeah, you know,
he's right.
We can't forget it.
Fine. Now here's
the plan:
I'm taking Quagmire
for a little ride,
and you guys are gonna stay out
here and freeze to death!
Now, get those hands
where I can see 'em!
All the way up!
Oh, my shirt's a
little too short.
That's okay.
You can keep 'em
the way you had 'em
so it covers your stomach.
Thank you. You know, if
this Jeff was around more,
we wouldn't have
tried to kill you.
See you later,
schmucks!
All right,
this is far enough.
Well, Quagmire, sorry
it had to end this way;
a tragic hunting accident.
I guess that little baby's gonna
grow up without an uncle.
Actually,
I have a brother.
Gary Quagmire.
Oh.
I think... I think you got
a brother, too, don't you?
All right, forget
the uncle thing!
Get ready to die,
Quagmire.
You know, if you had any balls,
you'd put that gun down and we
could settle this like men.
(laughs)
That's awful big talk for a
scrawny bastard like you.
Hey, I'm serious, man.
Unless you're scared
I can take you.
Suit yourself, man.
Just means
you're gonna die slower.
(spits)
(bones crack)
(gasping)
(groans)
(engine starts)
(engine revs)
What the hell?!
I killed you!
I choke myself every day,
you bastard!
(tires squeal)
(radiator hissing)
(sobbing)
Oh, oh, Glenn,
there you are.
Jeff didn't come home last night
and he hasn't called.
Uh, well, actually,
about that, Brenda,
he must've left
early this morning.
Yeah, we found this
note he left you.
"Dear Brenda,
I have decided to leave you.
"I realized
that you are too good for me,
"and you and our unborn child
would be better off
"without me in the picture.
Love, Jeff.
"P.S. If the cops ask, tell them
"that Joe, Peter and Quagmire
were with you last night.
"If you tell anyone otherwise,
"I will come back and not only
hit you, but I will murder you.
"And no one will care
because you're garbage.
And your baby is going
to be a child of garbage."
(hushed):
It's a little rough, Peter.
I didn't write it. Joe did.
I wanted it
to sound real.
It's gotta sound
like he wrote it.
Plus, she kinda is
garbage, Quagmire.
"Well, I best be
rolling on now."
(hushed): Oh, come on!
Who says that?!
(hushed):
It's an expression.
Yeah, if you're in
a wheelchair.
Listen, you had
your chance.
I e-mailed it
to both of you.
You wrote back:
"Looks fine."
And you just added that
part about Grape Ape.
"P.P.S. I really love Grape Ape.
The end."
(sighs) Wow.
I guess he's really gone.
(sobbing)
I kinda want to kill
somebody else now.
Ooh, Mort!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru